Marek Przybylek

Account Development Manager at Brand24

Summary

Experienced Account Development Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Management, Customer Service, Account Management, Sales, and Business Development. Strong sales professional with a Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.) focused in Clinical Psychology, Business from American International College.

Experience

Account Development Manager at Brand24

Account Development Manager at Brand24 March 2015 - Present

Account Development Specialist at GetResponse January 2014 - February 2015 (1 year 2 months)

Education

American International College Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Clinical Psychology, Business , 2005 - 2013

Marek Przybylek

Account Development Manager at Brand24



Contact Marek on LinkedIn